

# SEBASTIAN PRADO

FULL STACK DEVELOPER / AGRICULTURAL ENGINEER

# **SUMMARY**

Former agricultural engineer turned Full stack web developer..

After 8 years in the agricultural industry, I decided to embark on a new career in web development . My background in agricultural engineering has honed my problem-solving skills, attention to detail, and ability to optimize processes.

I am a highly self motivated individual who is able to work both independently and as part of a collaborative team.

# **TECHNOLOGIES**

- HTML.
- CSS.
- JavaScript (ES6+).
- NodeJS+ Express.
- React + Redux.
- MySQL and MongoDB.
- Git.
- Insomnia

# **LANGUAGES**

- Spanish (Native C2).
- English (Superior C1 / PTE 85pts / CAE band 8 ).
- Portuguese (Competent)

# CONTACT



+61 455 234 514 (Aus).



sebastian.pradomelesi@gmail.com.

https://pradosebastian.vercel.app/



@SebaPrado



# **EDUCATION**

#### Coding Bootcamp - Full Stack Web Developer

Hack Academy | Jan 2024 - Apr 2024

Full-time educational course, extremely hands-on and intensive.

Total hours: more than 600 hs.

Technologíes: HTML, CSS, React, Node, MongoDB, MySQL y Git. Final project: e-commerce site (https://equalvision.vercel.app/).

#### Front-End course

Hack Academy | Nov 2023

Total hours: 80 hs.

Technologíes: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap.

### Agricultural Engineering Bachelor degree.

UDELAR University | 2009 - 2013

100% completed.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Full Stack Web Developer. | Aug 2023 - Oct 2024.

pandape.com.uy

• Frontend development

juegos.agesic.gub.uy

· Frontend development

#### loi.com.uy

- Frontend development
- Database development

# Equal vision e-commerce

- Database modeling
- UX/UI design.

#### Agricultural engineer.

Yaloak estate, Vic. Australia | Jun 2021- Ago 2023

- prescision agriculture technician.
- crop advisory.

Private agricultural advisory | Jun 2019 - Oct 2020

• Developing Sustainable Dairy Land Plans, focused on the calculation of soil loss related to hydric erosion.

Maize seed chamber, Uruguay | Mar 2018 - Mar 2019

- Elaborating proposals to reduce the impact of agricultural activity on the contamination of water courses.
- Controlling agricultural practices related to IRM (Insect resistance management)

## **REFERENCES**

#### Programming

• Facundo Irazusta - Hack Academy

Whatsapp: +598 96 110 111

#### Australia

• Rob Binks - General manager . Yaloak Ag Co

Ph: + 61 428548511

• Stuart Booth - General manager. Caldermeade farm

Ph: + 61 435779748